Thank you for watching!
Thank you so much for everything!
This time, we will be talking about Morning Musume。 Stay, this time with Akemi Haga of Morning Musume。 23's Akane Haga and Juice- Juice's Sakura Ishiyama.
These two will be presenting this time, so please stay with us until the end.
Please bear with me until the end.
Well, the other day, I was at the Morning Musume。 23 25th Anniversary Concert Tour
Grad Quarter Century at Nippon Budokan has just ended.
Thank you to everyone who came to the concert and to those who watched the live broadcast and live viewing.
This Halo! I can't talk about my impressions of the concert yet, since it was recorded before the Nippon Budokan concert,
I think it was a very exciting 25th anniversary show.
The Nippon Budokan concert also marked the unveiling of the new members.
We, Morning Musume。 23, we have two new 17th term members, Haruka Inoue and Ayako Yumokeda,
I am really looking forward to seeing what kind of combination they will show us.
And Juice-Juice also has a new member, doesn't it?
Yes, Mifu Kawashima joined Juice-Juice.
She is a very pure and cute girl, and when she talks, she is very fluffy,
She is very pure and cute when she talks, but when she performs, she shows us how cool and proper she is,
I have a lot to learn from her,
I have a lot to learn from her, and since I am her first junior member, I feel that I have to keep growing up.
I saw you cry a lot at Juice-Juice's performance at Nippon Budokan.
Seeing her crying, I cried a lot by myself in the audience,
I thought Mifchan was so cute like that.
I hope you are looking forward to the growth of the new members and our activities under the new organization.
I look forward to your continued support.
I will also be participating in the "Halo! I am sure that the performance at Nippon Budokan will be broadcasted on Halo!
Please watch this video first.
Here we go!
Take-chan!
Yes!
Riko!
Leila!
Kiro!
Tame!
Okanyan!
Rey!
Game on!
Whoo!
Yeah!
Ooh!
City of noise I'm going with the flow
My midnight
I'm already embarrassed
I don't know why the voice messages
I don't say it but I hear it
It's not a secret.
How many times was it? The urge...
The bottom of your pocket.
A place to hide my true feelings.
I shiver. What's waiting for me?
I'm anxious to play with your lips.
I wish you'd notice me more
Oh oh oh oh I need a hug
I can't be bothered
I can't stand the mannerisms that linger in your mouth
Let's fall in love again
If I could cry
I'd cry all day long
I'd like to meet youI want to meet you!
I want to meet you
caught in the rain
Breathe in the rain
I'm holding my mouth closed
I wonder whose face I'm asking
Ah
I don't listen to the messages, I just keep following them
I'm scared of something, the night before, the night after, the night before, my head hurts so bad
I can't move when it hurts
My mind is always on my feet.
My hair is looking right through me Manger mode I'm so timid
Oh Oh Oh Oh
I'm so selfish I don't want you to hate me
My hair sees through, manger mode, timid love
Oh Oh Oh
The wind that blows away, the voice that drowns out
I'm so, so, so lonely
Gently lubricating my throat
Oh Oh Oh
The reluctant way, the eternal, the face of time
I kept my mouth shut lest it be taken away from me In the end
Feel the biting goal Manner mode
Oh, give me your neck Oh Oh Oh
Even if I'm being selfish
Me
The wind that blows and the voice that drowns out
Very, very, very lonely
Let's dance, softly
Full throttle
Thank you for everything. I'm cheering for you too.
Morning Musume。 23's Akane Haga and Juice-Juice's Sakura Ishiyama present "Halo! Station.
From here, we would like to talk a little about each other.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so please answer them without thinking too much.
So, here we go.
Sakura Ishiyama says she likes to shop alone. What is your latest nice purchase?
Sneakers.
Her second new single since joining the group will be released on July 12.
What do you think has made Sakura-chan matured since her last single?
She danced a lot.
A commemorative event is also being held to celebrate the release. What is a release event like for you?
It's a place where I try my best to get people who don't know Juice-Juice to stop by.
What color of clothes do you often wear?
Black.
This Halo! STE will be distributed on June 28, so tomorrow, on June 29, it will be exactly one year since I joined Juice-Juice.
What is the first word that comes to mind when you look back on the past year?
Effort.
Thank you very much.
So, I would like to ask you, did you make a lot of final efforts?
When I first joined the company, I had a hard time learning how to dance and sing, and there were many days when I wondered what to do,
But I watched the videos of the older members every day and watched the Huri V videos, and I think I did a great job during the year,
I also made an effort to grow up and work harder since I had new juniors for the first time.
They are wonderful.
I asked her what color of clothes she often wears. When I looked at Juice-Juice's Instagram, I got the impression that she wears a lot of different colors,
But I still think black is the best.
In the end, yes, I still wear a lot of black.
When I post on Instagram, I try to wear colorful clothes as much as possible.
That's right.
I often take pictures when I wear colorful clothes,I often take pictures when I wear clothes that have colorful colors on them,
But I still think black is the most common color.
I wear black a lot.
I see. Thank you very much.
So, we will take questions for Ms. Haga after the VTR.
Hello! Ste.
Love you! We are brave!
Earth is a foreign meat business to begin with!
Feel the use!
Maine Eva! Beast of love!
Now on sale!
I love you!
I'm sorry I doubted you!
Now on sale!
I wanted to love you, I couldn't love you
I won't kiss you if it's okay
I couldn't even tell you
Pride Bright July 12 on sale!
Is it because of the summer? Is it a dream?
A little unstable
Now a new single!
Slightly Emotionally Unstable Summer
July 26 on sale!
Yokohama Arena has ended!
Thank you very much for your support.
Thank you!
How was Linny?
Well, I said on stage that I was suddenly starting to feel it,
But now I don't feel it at all.
What?
You're back?
I'm back.
I don't know, I haven't seen the survey without Mr. Takeuchi yet.
Maybe he's not coming.
The next one is for work, and Takeuchi-san isn't here.
I think it's strange that he's not here.
I don't mind if you go visit him.
I can go, though. I was thinking of going.
Yes, that's right.
How was it?
It was a lot of fun.
It was the moment when one of our dreams came true,
I was really too happy.
I'm so happy, I'll probably be a teenager tomorrow.
I can understand that.
It was fun.
I really feel like I've done everything already.
I have been through a lot in the 12 years since I joined this birth,
But standing in Yokohama Arena at the end of the show, I really felt that I was protected by everything that I have done so far,
I feel that everything I have done up to now has been protected.
Thank you so much.
I will continue to do my best for Angelem and myself, so please support us.
That's all for now.
Thank you very much.
Halo! Sta.
Next, I would like to ask a question to Ms. Haga. Please give me your best regards.
You are crazy about film cameras, so if you were to take pictures of the new members, what kind of scenes would you like to capture?
Haruka would like to take pictures of shaved ice, and Ako would like to take pictures in the forest.
What is the key to today's fashion?What are the key points of today's fashion?
My sister told me it was really hot, so I focused on the temperature.
What are you currently doing to improve yourself?
I eat more protein.
What is the key to today's makeup?
It's this pulled-together lip that I got from Maria of Tamaki.
It's cute.
What kind of work or performance would you like to do someday, Mr. Haga ?
Is it shinobue?
Shinobue.
Thank you very much.
I was wondering why shinobue?
What is shinobue?
Shinobue is a flute that is often heard along with taiko drums in o-hayashis and the like.
The flute that sounds like a "huru-huru" is a shinobue.
I used to play it as a club activity when I was in elementary school.
I decided to give it a try for the first time in a long time when the 2020 self-restraint period was in effect.
I never got that deep into it.
But I still think it's cool that people can play instruments.
So I still want to be able to play an instrument.
That's great.
I would love to hear your shinobue.
I will try my best to do it.
So, what should we do next if we were to take pictures of a new member with a film camera?
Shaved ice.
I asked Haruka what her favorite food is, and she said shaved ice.
I also like shaved ice a lot.
I thought it would be really cute to have a scene where we eat shaved ice.
Ako-chan is in the forest.
She is wearing a straw hat and looks like a forest fairy.
I would love to shoot in a place where there is sunlight.
I have great expectations. I'd like to shoot it someday.
Hallo! There's more to come after this.
Shaved ice! Shaved ice! Shaved ice!
I wish I could show you now
I want to show you the view I see in my eyes
When the dream began, I was still a child
I turn around and cry for so long
I've been on the road for so long
I couldn't do it right
I cried because I couldn't do it right
That's how it happened in the beginning.
I remember.
Once you're in front of me, all my strength
Scary nights.
You can walk now.
I have to go.
I can't find it.
Cause I'm the only one waiting for answers
I sang the song over and over again without showing it to anyone.
I sang it over and over and over again
I want to show it to the me of that day now.
The future that I dreamed of, the future that I dreamed of
Where is it shining?
I've got a new dream, a new dream
If I don't do anything, I won't be able to move forward with these thoughts.
I have to make a decision. I'm very happy about it.
But it's also a little bit sad, isn't it?
I love you and I want to leave you...
I don't hold my heart a little bit.
I'm happy, I'm frustrated...I'm happy, I'm frustrated.
I put my heart and soul into every step of the way.
I danced many times without showing it to anyone.
I danced over and over again.
With myself in the mirror
I wonder if the me of that day
I wonder if you're smiling at me
I wonder if you'll smile at the day I arrived
Smile, smile, smile
I hope you've got my heart on your chest
The little light that I kept on lighting
Floating in a mist of light
It's a sparkle, it's a sparkle, it's a sparkle, it's a sparkle
Lighting up the way It's time to take the first step
I want to show it to the me of that day now
The future I dreamed of, the future I dreamed of
I loved to sing I loved to dance
That's all there was, that's all there was
I want to see it with the me of that day
The future I dreamed of, the future I dreamed of
It's shining right here
I gotta go, I gotta go, I gotta go, I gotta go, I gotta go
I have to go, I have to go, I have to go, I have to go, I have to go
Now, I would like to express my gratitude to all of you.
First of all, thank you so much for all your support until today.
And this is no good.
The last time in my life as an idol, I was in such a wonderful place,
And thank you so much for showing me such a wonderful view.
It has been 12 years since I joined S/mileage and 15 years since I joined Halo Pro Egg.
I didn't think I would be doing this for so long, and to be honest, I'm the most surprised that I've been doing this for so long,
However, I am most surprised that I have been doing this for such a long time, but it is because I have received so much passionate support and so much love from everyone,
I think that is why I have been able to make it this far.
After I announced my graduation, I once again had a thought,
I am happiest and most enjoyable when I am performing live.
I think I shine brightest when I am on stage as Angstrom,
I loved myself like that the most.
I'm going to cry. I don't know if I can do it.
Thank you so much for making me an idol.
No!
I'm going, aren't I?
And it's because I've been active for such a long time,
I have met such lovely and loving sisters.
To be honest, I will miss them more than ever from now on.
Why do I cry so much?
Yeah, I'll do my best. Thank you.
Yes, really, I'm going to miss you guys so much more than ever,
But when we first joined the band, you guys were so timid and sometimes stood on stage with an anxious look on your faces,
But when I realized how cool and cute they were, and how reliable they had become.
That's why I'm really looking forward to the future of Angelem.
I'm sure you are too, right?
From now on, I think we will face many difficulties that we have never faced before,
I am sure there will be many difficulties that we have never faced before, but we will all believe in each other and go forward on the path that we all believe in,
I hope that everyone will continue to create a new form of Angelem together.
I hope that everyone will continue to create a new form of Angelem, and break down various barriers together,
Please continue to renew the strongest Angelem!
And as for me, I am going to aim for the world as my first move.
I would be lying if I said that I am not anxious,
But I'm looking forward to it more than that, and I'm very excited about it.
I hope that people will think that Take-chan is amazing and that Takeuchi is the strongest,
I'll continue to do my best, so I'd be happy if you could leave my presence in a corner of your mind,
I would be very happy if you could keep my presence in a corner of your mind.I would be happy if you could leave your presence here.
I'll tell you one more thing that will make everyone very happy.
Listen to me. Okay?
It's me. I'm going to keep singing!
Oh, wait, wait, wait, yes, sink, sink, sink.
I'll dance!
Quiet once more, quiet once more.
That means I'll be back on stage again!
Yes, I'll be back on stage again!
I was told this before I graduated.
Take-chan, please sing. Please come back to the stage after graduation.
I said I would consider it,
Well, everyone was saying too much, so I told you here!
So I am sure we will be able to meet again,
I am sure we will meet again, so I hope you will be patient.
I wish you all the best in the future!
Thank you very much.
So, this is the last time,
Thank you for all the love and happy time you have given me over the years~!
Let's do our best again tomorrow!
Morning Musume。 13's Akaon Haga and Juice- Juice's Sakira Ishiyama present "Halo! STE!
Project is celebrating its 25th anniversary this year. Project celebrates its 25th anniversary this year!
Project is celebrating its 25th anniversary this year. Project and Juice-Juice are now in their 25th anniversary year, aren't they?
Yes, it is.
This time, we would like to share with you some of our favorites from the 25 years of Hello! Project's 25 years of music, we would like to introduce to you a music video that we have selected as one of our favorites.
Yes, I'm Akemi Haga.
First of all, I, Akemi Haga, would like to start.
The music video I've chosen is "Morning Musume。
123 by Morning Musume。 123 by Morning Musume。
This song fits my definition of "totally cute" perfectly.
But first of all, the name "123" appears like this.
Then it disappears and the song starts.
Then it disappears and the song starts, but then the members' bodies are shown.
I love how it makes me excited.
What's cute is that the members are like dolls or their poses are like dolls like this and they look at one point and look away.
They look like dolls or something, but their poses are a little bit like this, like they're staring at only one point, and their eyes are averted a little bit.
And the way she looks so young in spite of the heavy make-up and the real estate.
This song is really cute, and it was the beginning of EDM, so I think it has an image of a cool song.
The music video is also really cute with big ribbons and many ribbons on the costumes.
The music video is also very cute with big ribbons and many ribbons on the costumes, and the music video is very sparkling and cute.
1. shabbily and anxiously
2. stick together tightly
3. a little more patience
You are waiting
1. because you want to be cared about 2. because you want to be touched
2. you want me to touch you
3. you want me to smile
You wait
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I love you, I love you, I love you
No matter what, no matter what
I'm on your side now
I love you
I believe in you.
Hello! stee!
Sakura Ishiyama's choice for the most adorable music video is Country Girls' "Koi Dorobo"!
I thought everything about this music video was so cute from the first time I saw it, but I've summarized two things about it.
The first one is during the lip scene, when the camera is looking up from above and the members are looking up at each other, I thought it was really cute.
The second point was the B-melody of the first song, when the singer came out with bumpy and cute poses, which made me fall in love with the song.
It's so cute!
I'll never forgive you!I will never, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever allow that.
He's gonna get inside my head.
He's gonna get into my head, and everything I know is gonna be him.
I'll never forgive you.
I like that it's not easy.
He's dangerous.
Tection, there's nothing you can do.
♪ Ready in three, two, one, to monopoly in three, two, one ♪
I'll hold you in my arms and we'll goof off in three, two, one.
Hallo! Ste.
Morning Musume。' 23's Akaon Haga and
Juice-Juice's Sakura Ishiyama will be presenting "Halo! STE!
It's time to say goodbye!
Here is an announcement!
Project 2023 SUMMER CITY CIRCUIT Project 2023 SUMMER CITY CIRCUIT
will start on July 15th in Fukuoka!
This show will be an encore performance of the spring tour.
Project 2023 SUMMER CITY CIRCUIT is an encore performance of the Spring Tour!
Let's continue the fun live performance from the spring tour!
Juice-Juice's 17th single
Pride of Light Funky Flashing
will be released on July 12!
Pride of Light is a cool song that is typical of Juice-Juice.
and "Pride of Light Funky Flashing" is a cool song that is typical of Juice-Juice.
Pride of Light Funky Flashing is a refreshing and summery
and Pride of Light Flushing is a summery and refreshing song.
And on August 13th
Rockin' Japan Festival 2023!
Hello! Project is pleased to announce that
Morning Musume.' 23 Angulum
Juice-Juice, and Airi Suzuki will join us!
Let's make this summer hot again!
Juice-Juice will be performing at Tokyo Idol Festival 2023.
Juice-Juice will be performing at Tokyo Idol Festival 2023!
Juice-Juice will be performing on August 4!
We will do our best to make this summer a lot of fun!
We will do our best!
The "Halo! Project members will appear more and more on this channel.
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel.
In this meeting, Morning Musume。 23's Akemi Haga and Juice- Juice's Sakura Ishiyama.
Farewell.
The Yokohama Arena concert has ended.
No, really, it's still right after the show,
It was such a fun concert that I don't feel like I've graduated at all,
It was so much fun that I don't really feel like I graduated at all,
It was a very fulfilling day for me,
It was the very last live, so I thought it would be a memory that I will never forget,
Thank you very much for all the happy moments.
I was so happy and thankful for all the happy moments I had,
I was really moved by the blue penlights all over the audience,
I was really moved by that,
When I performed my solo song "I have to go", the color of the members of S/mileage was red,
When I performed my solo song "I have to go", there were many people waving red and blue penlights,
I felt that my life as an idol was loved by many people,
I felt so wonderful.
Thank you very much for your long time support.
Bye bye!
Let's end on a high note with this towel!
Get used to the days of shivering in the cold
Regain the temperature you forgot.
Why are you so excited?What makes it throb so high?
When the curtain rises so does it
It's so bulky.
How about we just leave it like this?
Take it all off
Ahoy!
I'm so dazzled
If I squint my eyes and look up
I'm so burning, by your side in the future
I'm so hot, I'm so disturbed, I can do it as one
Summer Shook I won't even offer a guess
Eyes high and shimmering shadows
Hot clouds are already ahead
Look up!
The time has come!
If you want to change, change now!
I find myself in a messy world full of contradictions
I'm so mad, I'm so sad, I'm so sad, I'm so sad
I'm in the habit of making things worse
Kakachu, you can do it without saying anything beautiful!
This year's tournament will be held at the Super Arena.
Let's join forces!
A festival that no one else can do
If it's with you, we can do it.
Up and at it!
Oh, I'm dazzled
If you squint your eyes and look up someday
If it's as far in the future as this year
Just by your side
It gets hotter
Like you're used to seeing
We can be as one
Summer Shook
We congratulate you.
Hey!
A.I. Nervousness dissolves, motioning violently
A.I. A.I. A.I. A.I.
A.I. A.I. A.I. A.I. A.I. A.I. A.I. A.I.
Change and start running You're the one who makes it happen, Meiji
The engine that starts the fire Sweat hard boys
If you notice even a little bit, you'll be a boy
Transformation Maybe I have to look sparkling
Joint Courage Stage
Feeling good? Feels good!
Let's take it in.
Everyone's smiling here.
Leave no one behind
Go!
Ah, look!
Ah, dazzling everything
If you look up with your cheeks dyed
As bright as this year
Sparkling by your side
Hot and dazzling
Like I'm used to, we can do it as one
Summer Shook
I'd like to recommend it to you!
Please subscribe to our channel!
The times are changing, the world is getting leaner and leaner
But you are always a friend to those who are too hotBut you've always been a friend to the overzealous
Even if they think you're out of date, you're still ruled by the same feelings that stopped you.
You're strong and strong and bright and big
You're always burning to lead the way
Shining in the middle of the scorching season
The strongest summer showcases
Come on, now, get it up
Oh, I'm dazzled, if I squint my eyes and look up
This local area, by your side so sparkly
It's gonna get hotter, it's gonna be a glittering night
Summer Shook, I'd like to congratulate you
I'm going to go right down the middle.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
See you later.